Well, in the last one, I showed you how
to get a sum of the villains um that
were caught. But maybe we want to reduce
this down to just the maximum number of
villains that any one hero caught. Um so
if we want to do that in a reducer, then
we're saying take the previous value and
the current value. What is the current
value? Well, the current value is going
to be this entire array right here or
this entire array right here. And so
what we want to do is we want to return
um the bigger number. So what we want to
do is we want to see if the previous
number is bigger than the current hero's
number of villains caught, then we want
to return the previous number.
Otherwise, we want to return the current
hero's number of villains caught.
And we'll start our count at zero
because no one in our array caught zero.
So if we save this and we reduce it
down, we get 20. 20 was the maximum
number of villains caught.
Um you could reverse this here. um just
by reversing this and that would give us
the smallest number of villains caught.
And if we come over, zero was the
smallest number of villains caught. Now,
if you look at our array, you'll notice
that zero is not in there. And why was
that? Well, it's because we said our
initial value is zero. So, what we want
to do is we want to set the initial
value to like a th00and because no one
in here caught a th00and. And if we come
over, it has now been reduced down.